many people being seen and few people being remembered
twenty-one days left for me to open a business
and i believe the easiest way i can
speed it up
is to pick up a skill
that I have and that I can teach people this
people do a lot in this digital world
is on
that's when I'm going to explain my idea
but we're going to put it in a more sophisticated format
put the music there
I've always tried to fit the seats
knows face
and the guys never gave me a chance man
it made me look like a man
I began to realize that for this Person
I was being interesting and not interesting
and then I got tired
I need to do something about this
I don't want to prove my worth anymore
I trust my job a lot
and i'm on
that i can be an interesting person
the only problem is what I do for the customer to notice this
thought I'll try to create a method
the beatbox was developed
for you to attract the attention of brands
customers
companies
business
e followers face
stop competing for people's attention
and I teach you
a how to attract
in fact what will save your business is intelligence
and when you hold your customer's attention
or your audience
what happens
you sell guy
ah Cayon
but how do i get the scar
of people the way you're talking
if you
manage to generate curiosity
in people
I guarantee you you'll get her confirmation
and through the cloud
that enters the next thing that is
be interesting and uninteresting Guy
and I will teach you
within 1 methodology that I developed
right here in this shed
with this pink cap and this dark circles here in Cara
more than
that used to make you interesting
and no one is watching you
wait there
here enter
be box
this one
is the gold
this would be worth a note
giving a summary because it won't get too long
then
I show you how not to kill your authenticity
and make money
dangers of you falling into other people's boxes
and then
the most important part of life bro
that money cannot enter
if joy has to come out
well that's what I'm going to teach in my workshop
glad I took a Red Bull
until tomorrow